scrubbu.com 2011-09-18

# Morgan Gold – BBB A Rating Accredited provider Gold IRA Plans – U.S. Coins Since 1963

**

Privacy Policy

Last modified: August 4, 2011

This Privacy Policy applies to all of the products, services and websites offered by Morgan Gold.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to [contact us](http://www.morgangold.com/contact/) through our website or write to us at

Privacy Matters  
c/o Morgan Gold  
19900 MacArthur Blvd. Suite 150  
Irvine, Ca 92612  
USA

Information we collect and how we use it

We may collect the following types of information:

  * **Information you provide**  – When you sign up for a Morgan Gold Account, we ask you for personal information. We may combine the information you submit under your account with information from other Morgan Gold services or third parties in order to provide you with a better experience and to improve the quality of our services. For certain services, we may give you the opportunity to opt out of combining such information. 
  * **Cookies**  – When you visit Morgan Gold, we send one or more [cookies](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cookie_\(disambiguation\)) to your computer or other device. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service, including for storing user preferences, and tracking user trends, such as how people search. Morgan Gold also uses cookies in its advertising services to help advertisers and publishers serve and manage ads across the web.
  * **Log information**  – When you access Morgan Gold services via a browser, application or other client our servers automatically record certain information. These server logs may include information such as your web request, your interaction with a service, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser or your account.
  * **User communications**  – When you send email or other communications to Morgan Gold, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services. When you send and receive SMS messages to or from one of our services that provides SMS functionality, we may collect and maintain information associated with those messages, such as the phone number, the content of the message, and the date and time of the transaction. We may use your email address to communicate with you about our services.

  * Protect the rights or property of Morgan Gold or our users.

If we use this information in a manner different than the purpose for which it was collected, then we will ask for your consent prior to such use.

Morgan Gold processes personal information on our servers in the United States of America. 

Information sharing

Morgan Gold only shares personal information with other companies or individuals outside of Morgan Gold in the following limited circumstances:

  * We have your consent. We require opt-in consent for the sharing of any sensitive personal information.
  * We provide such information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies or other trusted businesses or persons for the purpose of processing personal information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.
  * We have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Morgan Gold, its users or the public as required or permitted by law.

If Morgan Gold becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will ensure the confidentiality of any personal information involved in such transactions and provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

Information security

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, including appropriate encryption and physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data.

We restrict access to personal information to Morgan Gold employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to process it on our behalf. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.

Accessing and updating personal information

When you use Morgan Gold services, we make good faith efforts to provide you with access to your personal information and either to correct this data if it is inaccurate or to delete such data at your request if it is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes. We ask individual users to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes), or for which access is not otherwise required. In any case where we provide information access and correction, we perform this service free of charge, except if doing so would require a disproportionate effort. Because of the way we maintain certain services, after you delete your information, residual copies may take a period of time before they are deleted from our active servers and may remain in our backup systems. Please review the service Help Centers for more information.

Enforcement

Morgan Gold adheres to the US Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of Notice, Choice, Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity, Access and Enforcement, and is registered with the [U.S. Department of Commerce’s Safe Harbor Program](http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/).

Morgan Gold regularly reviews its compliance with this Privacy Policy. When we receive formal written complaints, it is Morgan Gold’s policy to contact the complaining user regarding his or her concerns. We will cooperate with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that cannot be resolved between Morgan Gold and an individual.

Changes to this Privacy Policy

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your explicit consent. We will post any Privacy Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of Privacy Policy changes). 

Morgan Gold · [About Morgan Gold](http://www.morgangold.com/about-morgan-gold/)

**

(Click here to find out more)
